/*global angular */

angular.module('mathSkills').value('data5_2', {
    title: '5.2 Identifying Factors of a Given Number',
    path: '5.2-identifying-factors-of-a-given-number',
    children: [{
        title: 'Choose the Factors of Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\html{Select the given divisors of 95 .}',
                answer: '\\css{\\grp{\\chk{1}{T}}{\\chk{2}{F}}{\\chk{3}{F}}{\\chk{5}{T}}{\\chk{7}{F}}{\\chk{10}{F}}}{factors}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\str{1 & 5}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Choose the Factors of Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\html{Select the given divisors of 136 .}',
                answer: '\\css{\\grp{\\chk{1}{T}}{\\chk{2}{T}}{\\chk{3}{F}}{\\chk{5}{F}}{\\chk{7}{F}}{\\chk{10}{F}}}{factors}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Choose the Factors of Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\html{Select the given divisors of 190 .}',
                answer: '\\css{\\grp{\\chk{1}{T}}{\\chk{2}{T}}{\\chk{3}{F}}{\\chk{5}{T}}{\\chk{7}{F}}{\\chk{10}{T}}}{factors}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Choose the Factors of Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\html{Select the given divisors of 160 .}',
                answer: '\\css{\\grp{\\chk{1}{T}}{\\chk{2}{T}}{\\chk{3}{F}}{\\chk{5}{T}}{\\chk{7}{F}}{\\chk{10}{T}}}{factors}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Choose the Factors of Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\html{Select the given divisors of 81 .}',
                answer: '\\css{\\grp{\\chk{1}{T}}{\\chk{2}{F}}{\\chk{3}{T}}{\\chk{5}{F}}{\\chk{7}{F}}{\\chk{10}{F}}}{factors}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Choose the Factors of Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\html{Select the given divisors of 59 .}',
                answer: '\\css{\\grp{\\chk{1}{T}}{\\chk{2}{F}}{\\chk{3}{F}}{\\chk{5}{F}}{\\chk{7}{F}}{\\chk{10}{F}}}{factors}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Choose the Factors of Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\html{Select the given divisors of 48 .}',
                answer: '\\css{\\grp{\\chk{1}{T}}{\\chk{2}{T}}{\\chk{3}{T}}{\\chk{5}{F}}{\\chk{7}{F}}{\\chk{10}{F}}}{factors}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Choose the Factors of Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\html{Select the given divisors of 145 .}',
                answer: '\\css{\\grp{\\chk{1}{T}}{\\chk{2}{F}}{\\chk{3}{F}}{\\chk{5}{T}}{\\chk{7}{F}}{\\chk{10}{F}}}{factors}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Choose the Factors of Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\html{Select the given divisors of 60 .}',
                answer: '\\css{\\grp{\\chk{1}{T}}{\\chk{2}{T}}{\\chk{3}{T}}{\\chk{5}{T}}{\\chk{7}{F}}{\\chk{10}{T}}}{factors}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Choose the Factors of Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\html{Select the given divisors of 94 .}',
                answer: '\\css{\\grp{\\chk{1}{T}}{\\chk{2}{T}}{\\chk{3}{F}}{\\chk{5}{F}}{\\chk{7}{F}}{\\chk{10}{F}}}{factors}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }]
});
